Hello everyone, today's
youth are known as millennials.
What is
special about millennials? They don't have
time to wait. They want to
get everything instantly. Then there is no
way for investment to be different. Then there
is a product that gives instant returns, that is, we invest and get pension return of income the next month. ICI
Credential's Gold Plan is its Gold
Ultra version. There
are four or five versions of this plan's Gold. We are talking about all these versions in
today's video.
Similarly, ICICI's Gold Plan is a plan that gives
75% IRR, that is, the highest IRR in this industry. So
watch the video till the end to know all the details. If this is
your first time watching this channel, let me
introduce myself. My name is Binoy. I have been in the
field of insurance investment and banking for the past 20 years.
[Music]
Working At the beginning of the video,
I said that there are many options in the Gold Plan. The
new additions to the Gold Plan are
Gold Ultra, which means that the
next month is now November 2024. This month is
November
24. The 20th date is November 20, 2024. This is the plan where
we start getting pension from December 2024 itself. Gold Ultra is called the plan where we start getting return of income, which is called
Gold Cash Back. There is
an option called Gold Forever.
After watching this entire video, you will understand the details about these options.
First, let's
look at the Gold Ultra option. I
said that Next is the
option where you get return income the next month itself. Gold
Ultra can be divided into Instant Income.
Next Income will then continue to
receive income until the age of 99.
That is, if a 35-year-old person takes it now, he will be
35 years old now, 15
years old next month and then every  You will continue to get
income till the age of 99. You will
get regular income and then it is a legacy creation. At the age of 99,
we will get a huge
amount. We will get
10 times the amount we invested. Let's
see how much we will get. Let's see
how the Gold Ultra option works.
Suppose a 35-year-old person takes a plan and takes a premium of
₹100,000 for 12 years. Now according to this example, if the
plan is issued on November 20, 2024, then on
December 20, 2024,
₹34,000 will be instantly paid and the
person will start getting income the next month. This is the first such
development in the industry. After that,
every year on December 20, the person will continue to
get ₹34,000 for the 99th year of the person's 99th year.  A
person will get Rs 1 crore 68
lakhs. In the 99th year, a person will get Rs 1 crore 68
lakhs as a legacy creation as
savings. This is the Gold Ultra
option. If you want to know how much you will get as per your age,
illustration of benefits. If you want to know
more details, you can
send me a whatsapp on the number shown in this video
or
call me on this number. How does this Gold Cash Back
option work? Let's
see with an example. A 35-
year-old person takes a plan. He pays a
premium of 10 per month for 10 years. He
takes a plan on November 2020 and 2024 at the age of 35. If he
takes the plan on November 20, 2024, he will get ₹33000 in December 2024. In
this way, a person will get ₹33000 income at the age of 36, 37, 38, 39.
This is the
difference in cash back at the age of 40.  At the
age of 15, ₹45000, so at the age of 55, ₹
45000, at the age of 45, ₹
45000, at the age of 50, ₹45000, and so on, every five years, you will continue to get
more income.
In between, 33000 will
continue. At the age of 99, 1
crore 46 lakh people will get an income. So, if you want
to know how much amount you will get according to your age and your premium, you can whatsapp me
or whatsapp this number.
Call me. If you like the video,
press the like button.
Gold Forever is an option. It means that
a person does not want instant income. I am
ready to wait. I want more
income. I want more return of return. I want
more pension.
Gold Forever is an option. As
mentioned earlier, a 35-year-old
person
takes a plan for a 35-year exam. He takes a premium for 10 years. The
premium is one lakh. From the 11th year, it is
one lakh.  The income will continue to be
received by the person. At the age of 99, the
person will
get Rs 76 lakh as savings and legacy creation. If you want to know the
illustration of benefits in your specific case, you can
send me a WhatsApp message on the number shown in this video or
call me. I can't wait until the age of 99.
I won't live to the age of 99. I want a lump sum of money quickly.
I was getting income together. I want a lump sum of money quickly. If you say "
quickly", you need it
after 30 years, 40 years, that is, a 35-year-old
person takes it. A 35-year-old person takes it. If you want it at the
age of 65,
we
have options where we can get a lump sum amount after 30 years. No matter how many years, 30 years, 35
years,
we can get a lump sum amount after we have completed a minimum of 30 years.
ICI is the best plan that a person who wants regular income plus savings can add to their portfolio.  Prudential's
Gold Plan IRR is the industry's best IRR plan with 75%,
so to know more about this plan or
to purchase this plan, you can
call or
whatsapp me on the number shown here. If you haven't subscribed to this channel yet, please
subscribe.
See you in the next video. Bye bye everyone.